Matthew D. Garrett

mdgarrett1984@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Team-oriented, professional with over 3 years of business analytics and IT experience. Strong skill-set in creative problem solving and interpersonal communication. Resourceful, intuitive, and results-oriented with a strong work ethic and a passion for tech innovation. Ability to adapt and learn quickly, prioritize, work independently, and consistently meet deadlines and goals

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration, Missouri State University, Springfield, MO

GPA: 3.0, Focus: International Business / Management, Minor: German, Graduated: May 2014

EXPERIENCE

Support Analyst, Cerner Corporation; Kansas City, MO 3/2015 - Present

• <u>Responsibilities include:</u> Supporting front end software issues, Analyzing critical software outages and infrastructure problems in a fast paced environment, Managing three different lines of service requests simultaneously, Coordinating with infrastructure teams to resolve issues in a timely manner

Acquisition Analyst, Garrett Properties; Buffalo, MO - 5/2009 - 8/2014

- Promoted to Acquisition Analyst in 2012
- In charge of marketing and appraising Commercial, Residential, and Unimproved real estate.
- <u>Responsibilities include:</u> Creating and distributing real estate brochures, Managing online advertising and social media, Identifying / analyzing acquisition opportunities

Group Sales Manager, Missouri State Tix; Springfield, MO - 8/2014 - 3/2015

- Promoted to Group Sales Manager in 2014
- <u>Responsibilities include:</u> Creating / cultivating strong client relationships, Effectively managing all large scale ticket sales for the university, Supervising front of house for event on sale days, Providing excellent customer service

Direct Solutions Supervisor, Missouri State Tix; Springfield, MO - 7/2012 - 8/14

- Promoted to Direct Solutions Supervisor in 2012.
- Gained strong foundation in sales and customer service both face-to-face and over the phone.
- <u>Responsibilities include:</u> Managing 30 ticket agents, Reconciling reports in excess of \$35,000, Accurately preparing internal audits, Creative problem solving, Analyzing large-scale report data

Web Development / Tech Knowledge

- Skilled in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Github, Google Analytics, WordPress
- Able to quickly prototype ideas and pivot to meet project needs, Acutely aware of current web trends and technologies, can easily traverse and manipulate the DOM
- Lead developer for headquartermagazine.com
- Skilled in Microsoft Office, Google Suite, and Windows and macOS